Guide to the Boardman Family Papers
Yale University Library
- PERSONAL PAPERS AND DEEDS, 1770-1936; Series IV; 22 boxes, 1 folio (10.5')
  - Personal Papers
    - Sheffield, Charles Joseph: estate records
      - 1897-1900 (Box 48, Folder 594-595)
    - Boardman, Mabel Thorp
      - Under the Red Cross Flag at Home and Abroad: typescript, ca. 1915 (Box 48, Folder 596)
      - North, Arthur W., The First Grandmother of Walton: Margaret Furman North, with a foreward by MTB, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 597)
    - [Boardman, Sarah Hall (Benham)?]: diary, 1862 (Box 48, Folder 598)
    - Boardman, Sarah Hall (Benham): estate records, 1870-1876 (Box 48, Folder 599)
    - Boardman, William Jarvis (1832-1915)
      - Account books, 1860-1907 (Box 48, Folder 600-601)
      - Account books, 1879-1914 (Box 49, Folder 602-603)
      - Bankbooks, 1892-1914 (Box 49, Folder 604)
      - Central Dispensary and Emergency Hospital, Washington, D.C.: printed matter, 1894-1911, no date (Box 49, Folder 605)
      - Checkbooks, 1885-1886, 1892-1893 (Box 49, Folder 606)
      - Claim Books
        - 1833-1897 (Box 49, Folder 607)
        - 1870-1886 (Box 50, Folder 608)
      - Land books
        - Ohio, 1886-1892 (Box 50, Folder 609)
        - Tennessee, 1857-1877 (Box 50, Folder 610)
      - Ledgers
        - 1857-1872 (Box 50, Folder 611)
        - 1890-1915 (Box 51, Folder 612-613)
      - Letterpress copybooks
        - 1859-1871 (Box 51, Folder 614-615)
        - 1871-1883 (Box 52, Folder 616-617)
        - 1883-1894 (Box 53, Folder 618-619)
        - 1894-1909 (Box 54, Folder 620-621)
        - 1909-1914 (Box 55, Folder 622)
        - 1859-1861 (Box 55, Folder 623)
        - 1861-1870 (Box 56, Folder 624-626)
        - 1870-1874 (Box 57, Folder 627)
        - 1864-1878, 1871-1873 (Box 57, Folder 628-629)
      - Memorandum book, 1865-1883 (Box 57, Folder 630)
      - Notebooks, 1866-1914 (Box 58, Folder 631-636)
      - Office docket book, 1859-1882 (Box 59, Folder 637)
      - Printed material, 1828-1911 (Box 59, Folder 638)
      - School notebooks: Harvard Law School, 1855-1856 (Box 59, Folder 639-640)
      - School notebooks: Harvard Law School, 1855-1856, 1874-1877 (Box 60, Folder 641)
      - Scrapbook of newspapers clippings: railroads, miscellaneous, 1859-1887 (Box 60, Folder 642)
      - Sheffield, Joseph Earl: estate records, 1882-1895 (Box 60, Folder 643-644)
      - Sheffield, Joseph Earl: estate records, 1882-1885 (Box 61, Folder 645)
    - Boardman, William Whiting
      - Account books, 1833-1862 (Box 61, Folder 646)
      - Bankbook, 1868-1871 (Box 61, Folder 646)
      - Daybooks
        - 1824-1855 (Box 61, Folder 647-648)
        - 1856-1871 (Box 62, Folder 649)
      - Estate records, 1871-1907 (Box 62, Folder 650-653)
      - Estate records, 1897-1907 (Box 63, Folder 654-655)
      - Journals, 1838-1860, 1871 (Box 63, Folder 656-658)
      - Land books: Ohio, 1816-1880 (Box 63, Folder 659)
      - Ledger, 1820-1867 (Box 64, Folder 660)
    - Schroeder, John Frederic (Box 64, Folder 661)
      - Address book, 1834-1837 (Box 64, Folder 661)
      - Notebook, 1832-1833 (Box 64, Folder 661)
    - Sheffield, Charles Joseph (Box 64, Folder 662)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1871-1886 (Box 64, Folder 662)
        See also: box 47, folders 593-595
    - Sheffield, George (Box 64, Folder 663)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1905-1908 (Box 64, Folder 663)
    - Sheffield, George St. John
      - Boardman, Elijah George (1868-1900), 1895-1900 (Box 64, Folder 664)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1868-1914 (Box 64, Folder 665)
      - Sheffield, Joseph Earl (1793-1882), 1879 (Box 64, Folder 666)
      - Sheffield, Maria (St. John), no date (Box 64, Folder 667)
    - Sheffield, Joseph Earl (1793-1882)
      - Boardman, Florence (Sheffield), 1869 (Box 64, Folder 668)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1860-1881 (Box 64, Folder 669-671)
      - Boardman, William Whiting, 1842-1852 (Box 64, Folder 672)
      - Sheffield, George St. John, 1871 (Box 64, Folder 673)
      - Printed tributes, 1882, 1907 (Box 64, Folder 674)
        See also: box 60, folders 643-645
    - Sheffield, Joseph Earl (1871-1903) (Box 65, Folder 675)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1902-1903 (Box 65, Folder 675)
    - Sheffield, Laura (Barnett)
      - Boardman, Elijah George (1868-1900), 1897-1899 (Box 65, Folder 676)
      - Boardman, Florence (Sheffield), 1896 (Box 65, Folder 677)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1895-1896 (Box 65, Folder 678)
    - Sheffield, Maria (St. John) (Box 65, Folder 679)
      - Boardman, William Jarvis, 1881-1885 (Box 65, Folder 679)
    - Sheffield, Nellie M. (Box 65, Folder 680)
      - Commonplace book, 1855-1856 (Box 65, Folder 680)
    - Wright, Cornelia Elizabeth (Schroeder) (Box 65, Folder 681)
      - Poems, no date (Box 65, Folder 681)
    - Unidentified
      - Account book, no date (Box 65, Folder 682)
      - Checkbook, 1928-1936 (Box 65, Folder 682)
      - Notebooks, 1848, no date (Box 65, Folder 683)
  - Deeds
    Folio
    - General, 1770-1914 (Box 65, Folder 684-687)
    - Oversize, 1811-1903 (Box 66, Folder 688)
    - Architectural drawings, maps, diplomas, 1854-1917, no date (Box 67)